JUAN MANUEL CERON ARAUJO

<u>Personal Projects:</u>
github.com/JuanCeron023

LinkedIn

CONTACT

(+57) 350 233 7416 Calle 16A #39-53 Pasto.

Email:

juanceron256@gmail.com

SKILLS

Programming languages:

Java
C#
JavaScript
HTML + CSS
SQL
Dart
Python
PHP

Frameworks:

Spring
Angular
Laravel
Testing:
Junit
Mockito

Databases:

PostgreSQL MySQL Firestore MongoDB

Others:

Scrum
Git
Flutter
React
Unity
Mayen

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native)
English (Advanced)
C1 APTIS CEFR
C2 EF TEST

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Systems Engineering student with 3 years of independent experience in software development.

I am a curious, organized person, passionate about software development, with excellent communication and teamwork skills. Always in search of acquiring new knowledge to be in constant growth at a personal and professional level.

EXPERIENCE

01/2021 - Actual

Software Developer of "Riesgos cardiovasculares UMariana" app Mariana University. Pasto.

- Development of a multiplatform mobile application with Flutter to calculate the cardiovascular risk of registered users, using Firestore as a database.
- Development of a web application with React to check and monitor the data calculated by the mobile application, using Material-UI elements for the interface and Firestore as a database.

05/2019 - Actual

Systems engineer student Mariana University. Pasto.

- Application development in Java, applying SOLID principles, with emphasis on the use of data structures such as lists, maps and set collections, implementing persistence through serialization and JUnit for the execution of unit tests.
- Development of web applications using servers on Linux and Windows systems, using Apache and IIS respectively, and deployed using Amazon EC2.
- Development of a Back Office in Java, implementing graphical interfaces and user profiles, using the PostgreSQL database manager.

01/2018 - 05/2019

Electronic engineering student Autónoma de Nariño University. Pasto.

- Development of a Back Office in Java for the organization and assignment of schedules and classrooms for the subjects of the electronic engineering program.
- Development of projects in Java, applying the principles of encapsulation, cohesion and decoupling.
- Development of a web application for medical appointments using Spring in the Backend, Angular in the Frontend and applying dependency injection.

01/2017 - 07/2017

Application developer in C# for Android Personal Entrepreneurship. Pasto.

REFERENCES

Santiago Ceron Araujo Conekta | Senior Developer Tel: 350 695 8883 santiceron023@gmail.com

Diego Paredes Reina Soporte Lógico | Business Unit Director Tel: 313 437 0049 dparedes@umariana.edu.co

Franklin Jimenez Giraldo Mariana U. | Systems engineering Program Director Tel: 301 580 7225 fjimenez@umariana.edu.co

Pedro Cerón y Cerón SAS | Sales manager Tel: 316 299 1712 pfceron2@hotmail.com

- Development of a video game with real-time interaction between the player, the NPCs and the stage.
- Developed in Unity, implementing in-app purchases and an obfuscator for code protection.
- Use of Autodesk and Blender 3D for the modeling and animation of the main character of the video game.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021

Systems Engineer, currently attending **Mariana University**, Pasto, COL.

2017 - 2019

English Level C1,

Cambridge Academy of Languages, Pasto, COL

Suan marrellan

Juan Manuel Cerón Araujo C.C. 1.107.520.417